let ques = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question:"1.What is the national animal of India?",
        answer: "Bengal Tiger",
        options: [
            "Lion",
            "Elephant",
            "Bengal Tiger",
            "Peacock"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2,
        question:"2. What is the capital city of Sri Lanka?",
        answer: "Colombo",
        options: [
            "Galle",
            "Colombo",
            "Jaffna",
            "Hambantota"
            ]

    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question:"3. Which country is known for its stunning beaches in places like Bali and Lombok?",
        answer: "Indonesia",
        options: [
            "Indonesia",
            " Australia",
            " Philippines",
            "Thailand"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question:"4. What is the currency used in Thailand?",
        answer: "Baht",
        options: [
            "Ringgit",
            "Baht",
            " Peso",
            "Rupiah"
        ]

    },
    {
        num: 5,
        question:"5. What is the name of the highest mountain in Sri Lanka?",
        answer: "Pidurutalagala",
        options: [
            "Pidurutalagala",
            "Mount Everest",
            "Mount Fuji",
            "Mount Kilimanjaro"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 6,
        question:"6. What is the tallest building in the world, located in Dubai?",
        answer: "Burj Khalifa",
        options: [
            "Burj Khalifa",
            "Taipei 101",
            "Shanghai Tower",
            "JAbraj Al Bait Clock Tower"
        ]

    },
    {
        num: 7,
        question:"7. What is the capital city of Indonesia?",
        answer: "Jakarta",
        options: [
            "Jakarta",
            " Bali",
            "Bandung",
            "Surabaya"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 8,
        question:"8. What is the name of the traditional Maldivian drum?",
        answer: "Bodu Beru",
        options: [
            "Bodu Beru",
            " Taiko",
            "Djembe",
            "Dhol"
        ]

    },
    {
        num: 9,
        question:"9. What is the famous street food in South Korea?",
        answer: "Tteokbokki",
        options: [
            "Bulgogi",
            "Jajangmyeon",
            "Bingsu",
            "Tteokbokki"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 10,
        question:"10. What is the traditional dress of Korea called?",
        answer: "Hanbok",
        options: [
            "Kimono",
            "Ao dai",
            "Hanbok",
            "Cheongsam"
        ]

    },

];